First, before publishing our Chrome extension,
to ensure that your extension folder contains unnecessary files.
So, we start from manifest my file containing name, description, version number, and permission.
And all the icons.
So, obviously, it's necessary because the icons will appear here.
We use, obviously, something else because when I load and packed a use of my Chrome extension,
that is, of the search, awesome with the search engine.
It has just default one.
In order to go through your change, it will be slim.
We can generate the tycoon in detectivity, then use image resizer,
and we will use developer dashboard.
If you don't have access to developer dashboard, you must log in to your developer Chrome,
and to actually upload an Chrome extension, you need to pay $5.
So, this is like an initial fee just to have access to all the ecosystem.
And that Chrome website developer dashboard access system will look like this.
This is the new item, notification, and here we will be able to add it.
So, first, I will go to my Chrome extension.
We have a manifest file.
We can even compare the manifest with something else, so, awesome multi-engine search.
And we can even add a question, so, I will just ask our users, and I will just ask now.
I want you to after my manifest and see if it has all information.
And you can add my name somewhere.
So, I can just type my name.
So, we see such a manifest update file, and this is actually necessary because, automatically,
it created icon.
So, we will obviously have to add our icon.
So, for the case, what I am going to do, I will use the order field that is here.
So, let's add it, so, please, I will switch.
So, press control dot, please implement, suggested, manifest JSON file, because I will add
this extension to a Chrome web store, that's right.
So, now, I will just make it another one, and we can work in edges, but for now in this
update file, so, this will be changed, and I will just add in my name, auto, and in the
meantime, so, if I go back now, we see it has been done, I can just create a new item,
and here we will be able to drop a zip or a CRX file, so, we can copy that over as well
after that.
All right, but first, we see we need some icons, because now, if we refresh it, we see
we don't have icons, so, we need to add the icons, because we have to add, so, it will
not be the default.
This is just like a workaround, we need a stick extension, and we don't want to add anyone.
So, first, I will just add, like, a awesome multi-engine search from extension, please, generate
image for this, there will be like a wrong image, we can try to use other models,
we can use up as a smaller, we can use standard banana or other, because now it's an
interesting area, so, we can even apply with Recraft, this is a nice tool, we cannot like
it, we can try to apply, so, now just log into it, and then we'll be able to get it.
So, first, we have a request, it will just generate all this accept terms, we see my dashboard,
a lot of this tool as well, so, it's a lot of stuff, and I can just specify for a logo,
and here, I can see, this is like an illustration art, this is vector icon that we can
use, there's a vector logo, we can actually apply to them, so, if you are searching for
some, because they have like many types now, we can type logo, and we'll be able to see
all of the logos, but this is just for a brand, this is like a shape stack, beautiful,
maybe you want to have some just icon, so, for that case, we can try to loose and look
for something, that will be good for us, this is for additional models, this is kinda
like it, because I'm a, what's generity icon for science fiction game, in the vector art
is nice too, so when I apply it, and now, when I have it, I can try to create it, so
I can just use maybe one image to not get so many colors, and now I can just apply
the web search engine on extension, logo, I can make it more specific, I can make it more detailed
and even put like a part of colors, I think the blue one would be the better to regenerate,
in the meantime, we can wait, oh, this is just a image for this, so this is actually
how it generated, but we have to specify that we need logos, this is a mistake, generate
a square logo for my from extension, that will help people use multi-end insert, now I would
just make another one, this is not the logo, and you can type even in negative quantity
don't want text, search logo with web, and in our colors, you can make something like this,
next simple icon is good too, this is not bad as well, because we can try to remove it,
like the white stuff, so here's the option, I think, to the selection, so we can use
specify, but I can download it, and obviously it will work like this, I can try to remove
it as well in another tool, so if I want to like move wide background, you can use this
one, this is another free tool, can upload the image that they have to know that, so
it's got the nose, it's just GPT, it will automatically remove the white, so now it has
removed all of it, and we have it that basically here, I can download it in the preview,
it doesn't matter, and here we have, I see like this one is not working well, but all
right, so I will just upload now, the one that I have very moved, is this, but keep
it in mind obviously that it will look like this, it will search engine, so yeah.
All right, now we just upload the image, here's my image, and if I go back to my, this
cursor, we see we need 16, 48 and 28, okay, so I will have to specify now the stuff,
so I will just use 128 and I will just export, you can just put one because it will give
the aspect ratio, actually you can apply more, but it's okay, so this is the new size,
and I will download the image, all right, as you can see, I have it already, but in order
to use it, we have to make the name like 16, 48 and luckily it's in PNG, so let's go
to use it, so the first will be icon 16, then it will be icon 48, and I'm on the one
will be icon 128, you can see if it's this size, okay, and now I can copy, so I will just
go to my cursor, and okay, we have icons, and I will open agents now, I will just open the
right bar, okay, so even if you recommended me actually a tool, so I can open it up and it's
like a five icon generator that we can use, so we can even specify our own icons that
I left you from here, I think it's a great tool, although it's sometimes this is better
maybe I think it's too generative because your feature is still created, okay, so now create
three icons, create them from a single design, they will face ready, but even if I go
now to the main review file explorer that is here and past it here, it's like I read
my file, regu file is not so interesting for me because it just shows how we can test
it, so I will just remove it will only like manifest and background, but now if I reload
it, so if I go back to my Chrome extension, search with, and I have this extension by
country, and by, and I search engine, so if I type like by do, go and try to look for images
that will give him here, and if I go again and try to search with my country, like, oh
sheen is even Bahamas, we have some bureau, I can go to Estonia, I'll be able to search
for like, in Estonia, okay, that's great, so now what I'm going to do, I will go to the
Chrome extension that I was now testing out, so it's awesome search, and what I'm going
to do, I will use background, icon, and copy everything except read me because I didn't
need this, and now I will just add to seven zip file, and after my seven zip file is finished,
I have to name it the same way, actually it's in the manifest, so if I go back to manifest,
we know that my manifest JSON, we see this file even here, it's awesome, multi-engine
search, and now I will just go and copy here, okay, I will make it to maybe the desktop,
I will go to the mouse and copy here, and now I will go back to my developer dashboard,
I will select the file, and this is awesome multi-engine search, it would first check if
I think it's the right, and I can even go to Chrome, web star, and see like, awesome search,
awesome search engine, and see actually that nothing pops up so we can freely use it, and
now it selects for category, so here we can just try to look for something, and I think
it's a great way, for example there's like, an extension sputnik that does similar things
but mostly for other stuff, so we can get like some of the requirements, support related
themes, and here we have our post dive, so we can select this accessibility, these are
the main categories that actually see, so this one is extension privacy, this one doesn't
have extension tools, we can go to tools, use this one, and the language we can see in
this page, this is the store icon, so actually if I paste it here, I think it will allow
us to make a store icon, okay this is not correct, so we have to go to the Chrome extension,
so I will go to desktop, my Chrome extension, awesome search, with the icon, here we can
add some of the screenshots, so the screenshots will be actually necessary, and then
we can add additional fields, I don't need to, because it just others URL, it can contact
some of it here, now we have a description, and that description, what I'm going to do,
I will just generate with mine, so if I go back to my main file here, I can ask, for
example, please, actually this video you can remove it manually, but I will just switch between
ask, I will upload this extension to the Chrome search engine, please generate me a brief
description, this is great because it knows great what is inside this code, so it will
just read all of the files, and then help us, great, so you see the description, you can
copy it over, then I will go back to my store list link, and that's it, and we can apply
some spacing, so people will be able to get a link, this, this, so we have this kind
of, I like it, and yeah, you can save us a draft, and keep that in mind, we have to apply
some of the screenshots, it's required, so we have to apply some of it, even if you see
this one, it has like a month's condition that we show, so for example, we are searching
for something, we can open some website to make it more visible, and we can go to Sumo,
and now I can use search, and show maybe some of the countries, and search engines, and
I will just create print screen, and now I can copy, actually I think it's better when
you make a screenshot without other extension, so what I am going to do, I will use
Extensity, and actually I can disable all of the extension, except the only one that I have,
I can use like, and it claims, okay, I don't see it here, so I will just go to my Chrome
extension management, and I will just use this one, and now when I have Sumo, and I will
just search, now I don't see other extension, I will go to Europe, and now I will, okay,
so I realized there is like an error, because some of extension has some weird IDs, it's
great, I think you have to test it more, so in order to do that we will just change
like one free CoA, and some of the United, so we can name it, I can even mark it, and
go again, and then I will ask your agent to create, as you can see, some of the countries
have weird IDs, and I will go again and basically say that by country, it's like one
free CoA, India, and I will need to, okay, please change it to the correct, the country,
so I will just apply quickly, hmm, and my package, I will just save it as a draft, because
you have a view upload, okay, save draft, it will be saved, and this is this extension
that I have published, but I will upload a new package, right, because this one uses
not good for our case, I'll just remove it for here, see actually if it's fixed, okay,
and now I can go to Chrome extend, now I can go to the Chrome extension, manage extension, I will
refresh it, and now when the package is ready, I will just test it, so now I will just
press Sumo, search with by country, I'll press Europe, and now we have beautiful IDs,
no errors like this, and I will go like that, actually I think Mozilla is not the best to
check, because yeah, they compete with Google, so maybe I'll just check it with maybe another
stuff, I will just go, I can use, I can use, I will just see maybe SolarPunk happening
in Africa, this climate drift, maybe the platform graphic or web browser, maybe we can go
even to GitHub, just to have it, okay, I can go to pause the I've tried intelligence,
and now when I'm in this website, I can just press like a dashboard here, and if I want
to see some such engines or Reoc, okay, this is just now, if I want to see something, I can
just press search, press by country, press by Europe, and we will go by it, I think it's
a nice search, now I can copy, actually I don't even need to copy, I can just save it,
so I will just save it as an image in the load, now it's a screenshot one, and below
I go over search engine, and here I search engine, can you make a line that will help users
do this thing, which hit from top 10 search engines, you know, I think I will edit because
it will help us to make it more organized, like a separator, right, not a line sorry, I think
it will generate really quick, so we will not have any problems, okay, this is the separator
global route, it will seem to file in context, okay, it's added, so now if I go to extension,
I will check it, and now if I go to domain, and search, oh, if you go, if you have error,
so go this and copy it or other, you can then apply some genders, obviously if something
is wrong we can go back, so we then need to give up, okay, now go back again, now I
just upload, so now I'll review, so this is the search engine that I used in the past,
and the zip file, actually it doesn't exist anymore, so just press F5 to refresh, and then I will
just make it to the zip file, and how you use osy mode soup, also, no type search engine,
I'll make it to the mouse, now have a search, and now we'll go back to the dashboard,
I'll go to package information, I will upload a new package, I will upload it basically here,
it automatically did the experiments because they are in manifest file, so we didn't need to edit,
so this is a global promo video, you don't need to use it, there's like a screenshot that you can
use, small promo tile, so I will pause the video and create all the graphics and then apply it,
this additional fits you don't need to add, and after you add graphical assets we can press
submit for review.